All men are created equal, but they are endowed by their creator with certain unalienable rights.
By liberty and the beauty of the world.
If liberty means anything at all, it means right to tell people what they do not want fear.
America, great again.
Welcome back to the Big Big Show. I'm your host Lance Miliaccio with my co-host George Ballantyne Rise and Grind doing what we do.
Of course, you know, this show is always tip of the spear because if liberty means anything at all,
it means right to tell people what they do not want to hear. And that is the plan on this show every single episode.
Hopefully we've done the research. We've spent all the time online using all our sources.
We've vetted the stories so that you have a place you can count on that what we're telling you is as close to the truth as possible with the information that's available.
Unlike mainstream media.
Jeez, the garbage today and the amount of BS I saw this morning.
And I'm always filtering at George and I look at stuff and I go, are you freaking kidding me? What is this garbage?
The controlled narratives and what they're trying to do to the current administration, you can see it.
And all I would tell you, be careful who you follow, be careful what you read, be careful what you believe.
A lot of this stuff is smoke and mirrors and it's always a planned operation in its own way when it comes to mainstream media.
And there's so many influencers. George, I don't know if you saw this one. There's just so many influencers I think are on the payroll because their narratives are so identical.
Yeah, I mean, especially with the tax, you know, they're going after like even bigger accounts.
I mean, that stuff with Insurrection Barbie is supposed to be all BS anyway.
So I mean, it's not stop Roger Stone, General Flynn, and it's the same.
I don't even want to mention their names, the same few, but I don't even know how people even listen to them how to have credibility.
You know, I was hopeful when they when they gutted USAID I was hoping that was the primary funding source.
But I think like many of the operations that the United States runs, I think there's a plan ABCDE in place.
So if USAID goes out, here comes the next one. And of course, they've got to wait a fun because it was funny right after USAID you guys might not have noticed this.
You would have seen a trend that a lot of accounts all of a sudden stop posting.
And then all of a sudden a couple of weeks later, everything ramped up.
And I always think, OK, well, they must have figured another way to pay.
You know, there's an agency in Chicago that's been paying a lot of them.
And I expected to see the name of that agency in Chicago listed on the USAID payroll. I didn't though.
So that means there's got to be a super pack or a foundation or an NGO or something else.
They figured a way to funnel the money through. You know, that's a lot where the black operations do.
They use different funding sources in case one fails.
And I saw that years ago about how the money would come in and the money was distributed.
So, you know, of course, we're planning on killing them with the truth and bearing with a smile.
Let's start off by thanking a couple of our sponsors.
Of course, original Glory beer. We appreciate these guys.
They've been with us the longest Mike Sadler veteran owned great company looking at expansion.
They've got their American Pillsner their American light and of course their new flavored light beer cheer in four different flavors.
Check them out. We'll have some stuff down the chat.
They're still doing the funding and they're planning on going national talk to your local liquor store about having them carry the product.
It's a great way to help Mike and the team out.
And of course, the guys over Genesis gold group.
All I can say is we've been telling you about gold and silver for a long time. It's an opportunity.
I think you always have to have, you know, always have something stashed just in case you need it.
I don't care whether it's a gold bag, whether you're a prepper.
You can look at it anyway, whether you're enjoying your second amendment rights.
You better always have a plan because maybe things aren't going to go the way they think they are.
And that's what gold and silver is all about.
This is the 62.2 gram prepper bar perforated easily broken down into your choice of three different denominations to fit a multitude of needs.
It doesn't matter if it's for asset protection from inflation, economic turmoil or its unique utility for barter and trade.
Prepper bar makes a perfect gift.
I mean, for everybody, there's nobody that doesn't like who wouldn't like to receive some silver or gold for a gift.
Is there any George, you'd love to get that for a gift, wouldn't you?
What? Break me off a piece of that prepper bar, Lance.
You know how I can roll.
Exactly.
All right, listen, that's the prepper bar, bigmigbar.com, bigmigbar.com.
Use all caps prepper for 10% off on the silver and 5% off on the gold.
Great company, great opportunity.
And it's a way to maybe protect yourself just in case.
And I want to thank the Big Big Mafia and of course the Bongino Army converts that have been coming in waves to our show.
We appreciate the support.
Let all those other Bongino Army members, if they're not happy with some of the current offerings on Rumble, we're here.
We're here to help you, Bongino Army.
Big Big Mafia, as always, we love you guys.
If you like the show, thumbs up, comment, share.
You know the routine.
You know what we need.
If you can do a paid subscription, fantastic.
It's five bucks a month.
It goes back in the show.
If you can do a Rumble rant, if you can do a regular subscription, we know it's a tough economy.
I'm not going to push you.
Do what you can to help support the show because we're going to be here for you.
I'm excited today.
We've got XCIA and founder of Panquake, John Caraco.
And I hope I pronounced that right.
Maybe he'll correct when he comes on.
It's a tough one at the airport.
John, just so you know, I know you're backstage.
Usually at the airport, my name is not Milliaccio.
It's Mr. Muchacho.
That usually is how it comes out.
He's a former CIA officer.
Let's bring him in, George, why I'm doing this bio.
That way he can be here and he can tell me if I got this right.
I used a lot of the search engines to get the information that I wanted.
All right, welcome to the Big Bang Show.
John Caraco.
Thank you so much.
Caraco, I think George got it right and I got it wrong.
He did. Good to be with you.
Good job, George.
Finally, he was a senior investigator for the Senate Foreign Relations Committee,
a courageous whistleblower who exposed the U.S. government's use of torture
under the post 9-11 counterterrorism program in 2007.
He became the first U.S. official to public confirm in detail
the CIA's use of waterboarding, sparking national and international debates
on intelligence, ethics, accountability, and human rights.
For telling the truth, of course, John paid the ultimate price,
became the only person jailed in connection with the CIA's torture program,
not for committing a torture, but for blowing the whistle on it.
He served 23 months in federal prison and emerges a leading voice
on government transparency, civil liberties, and institutional abuse.
Today, John is an acclaimed author.
He's got eight books.
I believe that's right.
John is eight?
Eight.
Eight books and that's unbelievable.
That's not easy to be a real author.
You have to write at least 14 to 16 pages a day.
That's true.
Yeah.
And he's a frequent media commentator.
He's had some great interviews on great shows.
He's talked about corruption, surveillance, abuse, and erosion
of constitutional freedoms.
He's one of us for sure, because you know what we talk about on this show.
John, first of all, thank you very much.
We appreciate it.
Thank you.
We know how precious time is.
So thank you so much for the interview.
The pleasure's all mine.
Thanks for having me.
We've had some other Christians in action on the show.
You're not the first.
I mean, of course, you know, having been around those guys,
I was around the DIA, the CIA, NSA guys,
and lots of other special operators,
Mossad, Scorpions, MI6 over the years.
I spent a lot of time around all of them.
It's interesting, you know, I think the guys in your age demographic
that were in the CIA came from a different time period
where maybe the CIA's charter was being followed.
I don't know how it turned into what it is now.
It's definitely gotten more complicated.
It's not the organization it started out to be.
No, sir.
And you face the consequences of that.
Maybe give people the cliff notes.
You came out, you wanted to talk about it,
and let me say something to the audience.
You know, having been around a lot of teams and operators
over the years, and there's not much you can really discuss
because they make you sign those agreements
that guarantees your prison time if you're too accurate.
I can tell you that there are a lot of things
that the agencies are doing all around the globe
that are not kosher.
I'm going to word it like that.
So what John came out with does not surprise me.
I'd heard all the rumors about that.
And I'd seen firsthand other countries
on how they dealt with interrogations.
I didn't see the U.S. directly.
I wasn't involved in any interrogations.
If anybody was, you know, picked up in a diplomatic security
or a facility security or any of the team stuff I was on,
you know, we didn't see what happened to them
after they got snatched and grabbed.
But I wouldn't doubt that these were the consequences
of their actions.
So John, let me give the audience some background
about why you whistle blue and then how they came after you.
And I want to say this in advance if I'm getting ready.
I know the story because I looked it all up.
You have to look at the weaponization of the system.
And if you're willing to go along with it,
kind of like when George and I were offered that,
we were offered 25 grand a month, John,
by an agency in Chicago that wanted us,
but they wanted to control the narrative.
We weren't supposed to talk negatively about Jews.
We weren't supposed to talk positively about Muslims.
We weren't supposed to talk about vaccine hesitancy
or the pandemic.
There was a whole thing, a whole,
and we weren't supposed to talk about election integrity.
There was a whole list of you can't do this,
you can't do this.
But if you do all this,
then we're going to give you more money.
We're going to give you the 25
and then we're going to give you more in three months.
We're going to give you a raise.
It was clear that they wanted a controlled operation.
And you faced the consequences of a weaponized government.
And they also came after me for a number of reasons.
And it had to do for me,
not wanting to go back to Northern Africa from,
if you want to believe that.
So, but go ahead, man.
Let's give the audience a story.
We'll start with that.
You know, in a nutshell,
and this is really the bottom line.
I am a constitutionalist.
I believe in the Constitution.
I believe that the Constitution
is a living and breathing thing.
Without it, we face chaos, anarchy.
And so when I returned from Pakistan to CIA headquarters,
I had been the chief of counterterrorism operations
in Pakistan after 9-11.
I was asked if I wanted to be trained
in these torture techniques.
I was the only person out of 14
who were asked who said no.
I said it was illegal
on top of being immoral and unethical.
And it just didn't work.
You know, I hate the FBI,
but I will compliment the FBI
in the respect that they have interrogations right.
They've been doing it since 1945
with the Nuremberg cases,
and they do it right.
The CIA was doing it wrong.
And now here we are,
24 years later, 23 years later,
and just this week at Guantanamo,
the military judge said that the information
that we were using against one of the prisoners there,
Amar al-Balooj, the son-in-law of Khalid Sheikh Mohammed,
cannot be used because the CIA
extracted the information using torture.
So these guys blew it.
They blew it in a big way.
And I just couldn't abide it.
And so I went public back in 2007.
It took them until 2012 to finally charge me.
They charged me with five felonies,
including three counts of espionage.
And you know, in discovery,
and I'll keep this very short, Lance,
in discovery we got three memos.
One was a memo from John Brennan to Eric Holder,
the attorney general at the time,
saying, charge him with espionage.
And Holder responded saying,
my people don't think he committed espionage.
And Brennan wrote back and said, charge him anyway
and make him defend himself.
So they charged me with three counts of espionage.
They waited until I went bankrupt from legal fees
and then they dropped the espionage charges.
Yeah, that's just for the audience.
Lawfare, that's a standard operating procedure.
So the two standard operating procedures
are under the initial indictment
that they try to deny you bond in every way they can.
In your case, I'm sure they were talking about you.
When they came after me,
they talked about me like I was 007.
Right.
You know, he's been to too many countries.
He's worked for agencies.
We can't, you know.
My feeling would be that you got,
they probably started with that,
didn't want to give you a bond.
Maybe you got a bond.
I hope you did.
250,000.
Yeah.
I have a question.
So I was going to finish yours.
Let me just, and then you can jump.
Yeah, just jump right in.
I just want to finish this thought.
I'm giving this to the audience
because they haven't been through this.
And then what they want to do
is they want to put you in a situation
where they drain your resources.
So they may freeze your bank accounts,
freeze your retirement accounts,
stop any payments.
If you were retired and you were getting payments,
they stopped those.
There it is.
And the number one answer way to do it is,
by you not having any money to defend yourself,
then you're stuck either defending yourself as a pro se,
or you can go with the next negative solution,
which is a public pretender,
also known as a public defender.
But that person will do nothing
other than do a plea negotiation.
And then usually what they do
when you're not complying,
that they offer you a deal that you think is unacceptable,
here comes the superseding indictment.
That's right.
Usually they threat,
or if they don't bring the superseding indictment,
they threaten you with the superseding indictment.
Repeatedly.
Right.
So they'll tell you,
if you don't take this deal,
it's the last deal you ever see.
And we're going to come up with three more charges
and you'll be looking at 50 years to life.
That's exactly what they did.
It's a non-compliance.
They never look at the substantive issues.
And then they give you what I call
is a massively curated set of discovery.
Of course, they go through the discovery
and anything that is exculpatory material
just disappears, gets destroyed.
You don't get that.
You only get the inculpatory.
And of course, in your case,
you bring up, you know,
when I think of Brennan,
I always think of Brennan, Clapper and Comey.
Three of the worst,
like Peter Strozik, another one.
Peter Stroke was the one
who actually put the cuffs on me.
You see, I mean,
these guys are just the scum.
I didn't know that,
but I got to tell you,
these are guys,
and this is what I understand
about the administration.
Then George, I'm going to throw to you.
I mean, I don't know what it takes
to get arrested as a government employer,
government official.
It seems like we only have unequal application
of the law.
There's no rule law.
There's no equal protection of the law.
And of course, the supreme law,
the land, just these guys,
just they think it's an inconvenience.
Yeah, that's right.
They don't treat it as such.
George, go ahead.
Listen, I don't even know
why they had the whistleblower protection act.
That means...
It's a joke.
It is a fucking joke.
And national security whistleblowers
are exempt from its protections.
Yeah.
Interesting.
So my question from your years of work
with CIA, your expertise,
what form of interrogation works best?
Obviously, we're not,
we don't want torture,
but what is it?
It's rapport building.
Sometimes it takes days, weeks,
even months,
but rather than tying the guy to a chair
and beating him in the face,
or waterboarding him,
you get so much more information,
good information, actionable intelligence
by offering him a cup of tea,
an orange,
if he's really cooperative,
a piece of paper and a pen
to write to his parents.
You'd be surprised what these guys
will give you.
When you treat them with respect,
it's really all it comes down to.
To him like a human being.
Yeah, exactly.
I think that if you really want to develop a source,
you have to develop a very trusting rapport.
If we were developing sources years ago
when we had to communicate with people,
you would try to develop a relationship
that was built on trust.
Probably the secondary successful tool
I saw was when people would say,
well, you need to help us,
or your family's going to have a problem.
Guys would usually,
that was a secondary that didn't require violence,
but just that they thought their family
or their parents were going to be impacted.
That immediately would get,
if you had to get to that point,
you could get some kind of cooperation at that level,
but you're right.
I think the soft touch always worked better.
Oh my God, there's no comparison.
If I could tell you a short little story.
If I blew the whistle,
I was approached by Liberty University
to take an adjunct role
as a professor at the Helms School of Government,
teaching Introduction to Intelligence
and Introduction to Intelligence Analysis.
The Dean of the school
gave a final exam that year.
That was so impactful.
It's been in my mind ever since.
It was very, very simple.
It was four questions.
There's a bomb that's going to go off
in a major American city.
You've captured a leader of Al Qaeda.
You know that he has the information.
You need to disrupt this attack.
Do you torture him?
Yes, no, and explain.
The next question was,
he didn't give you anything,
but you've captured his wife
and you know that she has knowledge
of the attack that's coming.
Do you torture her?
Yes, no, explain.
Third question,
the wife is a true believer,
but you have their kids in custody.
So do you torture their kids
to make the parents talk
so you can disrupt this attack
and save American lives?
Yes, no, and explain yourself.
The fourth question was,
you've died and you're at the Gates of Heaven
and Peter says to you,
come on in, Jesus wants to talk to you.
You go in and he says,
explain your actions.
What do you tell him?
It was such a simple example.
It was such a simple question
and it cut right to the core of this.
When they first called me,
I said, why would you want me to teach at Liberty?
We probably disagree on most of the issues
and without missing a beat,
they said torture is not Christian.
And so I took the job
and I was absolutely thrilled to be there.
Yeah, you know, it's,
but I think, you know,
if you look at the guys
that are involved in interrogations,
I often thought that mentally
they weren't capable of a sophisticated conversion.
You're exactly right.
You are exactly right.
On top of that,
there were no training courses
at the CIA in interrogations
and there was a very deep seated feeling
or a deep seated desire
for revenge for 9-11.
So instead of allowing the FBI
to just do what they're good at doing,
the CIA took over,
everything was classified above top secret
and there was nobody to stop them.
Yeah, you know,
and that's kind of the problem.
You know, the difficulty comes
when you're around a lot of those guys
or the agencies and team members and the rest.
You know, I often think that people,
I think one of the solutions I always lived by
no matter whatever business or what I was doing
is you always go to the toolbox
for the right tool, right?
And you don't use a screwdriver
where you need a hammer.
You don't use pliers where you need the hammer.
The problem with a lot of those groups
is they always think the hammer is the right tool.
They always go to the hammer
because it's a comfortable position.
They always, oh, let's go to the hammer.
Let's have him do it.
They never really think it through
that maybe there's multiple steps
where you still get the same result
without that behavior.
I think that a lot of times I think,
and let's face it,
the profiling when you're qualifying
to be in any of the agencies,
the profiling of the individuals,
the loner mentality,
disconnected from family,
the things that they look for, right?
Those don't necessarily make a sophisticated interrogator.
You know, the profile might as well say
sociopath disconnected from life.
And I think that's the tricky part.
I think that's the tricky part.
And we're not talking about analysts.
We're talking about the people
that are field agents.
So I don't know.
I'm concerned right now even, you know, George.
George has given until June 1 on the show.
We're concerned because I want action now.
I mean, I basically want the presidential letter.
I want a budget.
Let me pick out my teams and I'll go random.
You know, I'll go round up Brennan Clapper call me,
you know, Peter and the rest of them.
Because I don't think, yeah,
what I just don't understand right now
is the inaction in this current administration,
not that I don't think that going after trade data or Agua,
MS-13, and the Tesla terrorist is important.
It's got to happen.
I get it.
It's part of the problem.
Tom Homan is doing a great job.
He's amazing.
But above Tom Homan, I'm very concerned.
And listen, we've had cash on the show.
I think cash is a good man.
I just don't, I wonder who's holding him back.
I don't think this was his plan.
I don't think Dan Bongino had a plan to be held back.
I don't understand Pam Bondi.
She keeps talking about terrorists.
And I'm going, oh, she'll see some on social media
and she'll jump on that.
But then when it comes to some of these people,
the dirty 51 plus eight.
Oh, big deal.
We took their security classes.
So, so big fucking deal.
We know they committed a crime.
You know, the former Brett Tillman,
sorry, Brett Tillman, the former U.S. attorney in Utah
during the first Trump term said,
and this was his quote,
the Kiriakou case was the template
for the Democratic Party's policy of lawfare.
And I had convinced myself when Donald Trump won the second time
that he was going to clean house.
I was very optimistic about Pam Bondi's appointment.
And Cash Patel, we need Cash Patel
because we need somebody who's willing to shake the place up.
Dan Bongino, same thing.
Tear it down to the studs and rebuild it.
And we need somebody to take Cash Patel off the leash,
whatever leash he's on.
All right.
So, hold on.
So you might, I don't know.
They might not be on a leash.
We're three months into this administration.
Dan Bongino only got in an FBI what, two weeks ago.
Sure.
So, however the fact,
they might still have to be getting evidence
and building their cases.
That's a good point.
Because you can't rely on the old FBI
because you don't know what they did not put
in their reports or what's missing.
And you don't want to make it look like
I'm coming hard at the gate like a big revenge thing.
Because, you know, that's going to be their tactic
because Leticia James is saying,
oh, it's all bogus.
They're just doing revenge.
Yeah.
She said that yes.
That's a good point.
So, I mean, I'm giving them,
I gave them to next month, the first,
what is it, June 1st, Lance?
You said June 1st.
I'm giving June 1st to come up with something.
I mean, all right.
They did, but what is it?
Suggest charges on Leticia James.
And that came from the SBA part of the government,
whoever it was.
Yeah, FHCH.
So, let's see what happens with that because,
but we know, look, Schumer is holding up
the New York State Southern District U.S. Attorney
that Trump's appointing.
Yes.
He's holding that up.
You got, um...
They may kill the U.S. Attorney
for the District of Columbia.
Yeah, that's right.
Now they're accusing him of having been on,
well, yesterday it was extreme right wing podcasts.
And just to...
You're talking about Eagle Ed Martin?
Yeah, Ed Martin.
Yeah, I saw a show he did.
I saw a show he did,
and I was actually surprised he did the show.
I can't remember the name of it.
It was something DC, something or other.
But the only reason I was really surprised he did the show
is because he only, the guy only had, like,
maybe 1,200 followers.
He wasn't a big show,
and why Martin decided to do that show.
I'm not sure.
I think he had a policy of just saying yes
when people asked him to appear on podcasts.
No, I...
John, hold on.
I have a question.
This is...
Lance, I know you probably want to hear this too.
Sure.
One of the things I'm not happy about
with Cash Patel's direction
is appointing Jensen to lead the FBI
field office in DC.
He was like...
He was the one going after all the J-6ers and stuff.
I mean...
Yes.
I don't know if that's a setup
to make him look bad and draw him out.
I don't know, but I just want your thoughts.
I didn't understand that appointment at all.
And don't forget that
if you're the head of the DC field office,
the Washington field office,
or the New York field office,
it comes with a concurrent title
of deputy FBI director.
So he's not only the head of the Washington field office,
he's also one of the deputy directors of the FBI.
They have like four of them.
Washington, New York, counter-terrorism,
and then the principal deputy.
But still, however they couch it,
that seems like a promotion to me,
where a promotion is neither warranted
nor earned.
You know...
Laura Loomer was jumping out of her seat this morning
like she does, because she was ramped up about
the fact that they're not vetting the people around Donald Trump.
We saw that in the first administration.
I didn't like Pence from the second I saw him.
He just gave me a creepy vibe.
Yeah.
Same thing with Bill Barr.
There were so many of them that I, you know,
that I thought, right, Mike Pompeo,
I didn't trust her like him.
He was a dud.
So I agree with what she's saying.
They need to be vetted.
And I think the same thing with these agencies.
I almost wonder sometimes...
And I thought they did.
And you can correct me if I'm wrong, John.
I thought that as part of your vetting,
your social media was combed through.
Oh, my God, yes.
Even stuff is deleted.
Yeah, I would think that...
Yeah, even the deleted stuff.
We know that Graphica,
we know that the CIA is deeply embedded in Facebook.
We've seen through the Twitter files,
at least the ones that have been released,
that they're deeply involved in back-channel communications
with Twitter at that time and many other groups.
To me, it's pretty simple to find out
if you've got a never-Trump
or an anti-Republican
or an anti-Constitutionalist
looking at their social media.
These people have been very vocal in attacking
Donald Trump and attacking different individuals.
It would seem that the administration should just,
oh, shit, look at that.
He just called Cash Patel
or just said something shitty about Elon Musk
and Donald Trump.
Okay, no, we don't want this guy getting a promotion
and I don't even think we want him in the agency.
I mean, going in,
I remember Cash said he was going to make the FBI
building a museum.
Right, let's do it.
I mean, I believe we need a CIA
and I believe we need an FBI,
but I don't know that we need this CIA
or this FBI.
That's my concern
because they're not following the charter regulations.
They've got too many black budgets
that are available.
Leadership is bad.
I mean, we've had lots of ex-FBI.
We've had Kyle Seriffin on the show
and Garrett O'Boyle and Steve Gray.
Steve Gray, probably the perfect,
if I was going to make a nice square FBI peg
to put in a square FBI hole,
Steve would be the guy that I would want
running the agency and be involved in the agency
and he left because he felt like
they were turning him into a criminal.
He said they wanted me to be the criminal
and I went there to fight crime,
not to participate in crime
but the soup de jour at agencies.
They think they're above the law.
There's a terrible story
about some eavesdropping with Securus technologies.
I don't know if the facility,
were you on pre-trial detainment
or did they give you a bond right away?
No, they gave me bond right away.
With Securus, the phone company
that was providing services,
why you weren't here?
Well, Securus, if you go back to a case
U.S. versus Novak, they committed the,
in my opinion, it's the largest
criminal crime in U.S. history.
They've been eavesdropping on attorney client
phone call since 2006.
If you go type it in, you'll see it
and the federal government knows about it
but yet, nothing ever happens.
Nobody ever gets,
between absolute immunity
and the alleged
sanctions that the OPR,
PIN or the Civil Rights Division
are supposed to do, nothing ever happens.
This has been going on for years and years
and years. There's thousands and thousands
on all the legal phone calls.
Unbelievable.
The Civil Rights Division,
but they're still doing business with Securus.
Wonders never cease.
Outrageous.
All right, let's talk about this.
So when you were at the CIA,
what positions did you have?
What were your different titles?
I was there for 15 years
and I started out in analysis.
I was
in something called the Office of Leadership Analysis
for seven and a half years working on Iraq.
And then I got bored.
I had served overseas several times
in Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, Bahrain
and I got a little bit bored.
So I made a very unusual
switch to operations,
specifically counterterrorism operations.
I was fluent in Greek and Arabic
and then I went
through the operational training.
I went to Athens as a counterterrorism
officer. Then I
took a job training
Middle Eastern intelligence services
in counterterrorism operations
and then after 9-11 I went out to Pakistan
to head counterterrorism ops there.
Came back
and I was the chief of counterintelligence
in the Osama Bin Laden group
which was then called Alex Station.
And then I became the
deputy director
of the executive
assistant to the deputy director
for operations.
And then I finished up
doing counterterrorism at the United Nations.
Yeah, I got to ask you a question.
I don't know if you'll have the answer for this.
There was a lot of rumors about
Saddam Hussein, weapons of mass destruction
and at the root of
the real behind the scenes
with contractors there's a story about
Saddam using
this Shah's offset presses
to produce massive amounts
of
US counterfeit currency
and that he had
printed just literally billions of it
and his plan was to flood the market with that currency
to undermine the US
dollar. Now that was the dialogue
and of course you know about that group
of
I don't think they were rangers, I think they were just army
that got caught with
the cash and they got charged as if they were stealing
US cash but of course
it was counterfeit currency
and the US
government didn't really want to know that that's what this was really all about
that it really wasn't about
biological weapons, is that story
I don't even know if you can confirm that
they were parallel stories
both stories were true
so the counterfeit
cash, what we did
to counter that is we
we printed billions
and billions of Iraqi
dinars and we just
dropped it out of airplanes
yeah, yeah
people scoop it up
and crash the Iraqi economy
but so he had done, he had printed
that US currency because I heard he got
here's what happened, I thought there was a team guy
that I'd worked with and he told me about
that they were getting the paper out
of China and they were able to duplicate
and they'd even gotten the big head
and figured out a way to duplicate
the big head with the strip and all
but it was not of the quality that the North Koreans
or Hezbollah were producing
yeah, I heard that also
the North Koreans and Hezbollah produced
just perfect dollars, it was very
difficult to
to even realize that they were
how much of the US currency
on the open market do you think is counterfeit
because I heard a number of years ago
and I want to see if it matches
what do you think is counterfeit based on
because I understand the North Koreans are still doing it
yes
and it's all about the paper
the paper is produced in Switzerland
and if you can either get the Swiss paper
or match the Swiss paper
the printing is actually the easy part
gotcha
what do you think, how much US currency is counterfeit out there
of a high quality
I've heard that
it's as high as 5 or 10 percent
which just seems astronomical to me
yeah
but I will say that the Trump administration
has a policy now
it's a quiet policy but it's out there
of
paying 30 cents on the dollar
for
for these caches
of money
that are being found
all around the world and they're incinerating it
just to get it
off the streets
30 cents on the dollar, one of it's worth it
just to print a book
what's interesting
so I was with the group this is years ago
and the guy
that told me the story was MI6
and he said that the UK
had determined that they thought
that the amount of counterfeit
during that time period
we're talking about a while ago now
that it was almost 14 percent
they believed that the
US dollar was counterfeit
almost 14 percent
now again that was during that time period
when you were talking about
there were different countries that were printing
very very very difficult to tell
but they had come up with the conclusion
that they thought it was nearly 14 percent
and that's why it seemed like what
Saddam had planned
it could potentially work to undermine the US dollar
that was the big plan for him to drop
all this counterfeit money all over the globe
to move it all around
and then announce by the way
there's $50 billion
with the counterfeit currency in the open market
I know it for a fact
and then try to really destabilize the US dollar
all right let's make a short break
we'll be right back with John Kuroko
Kuriaku
and of course George Valentin
myself Lance Miliaccio
Mr. Muchacho
stay tuned
there's going to be a lot coming on here
we're going to be talking about lots of stuff
we're going to be talking about Panquake
stay tuned
as an American who keeps up with the real news
you know by now the severity
of the economic issues
that are plaguing our great nation
my name is Jonathan Rose
and I'm the CEO of Genesis Gold Group
the only major faith-driven company
in the industry
2024 is a year full of uncertainties
with trillions of dollars
in national debt
inflation impacting your savings
and the pivotal election year
your peace of mind is more valuable than ever
now is the time
to use physical gold and silver
to preserve your hard-earned retirement savings
with the Gold IRA
call Genesis Gold Group today
our team has decades of experience
helping folks just like you
take their first step on the path to true financial freedom
with the Gold and Silver IRA
call Genesis Gold Group today
at 1-800-200-GOLD
for a known commitment and formative consultation
with one of our experts
to find out if we can be a fit for you
call now at 1-800-200-4653
or visit genesisgoldgroup.com
in a world of uncertainty
be prepared with silver prepper bars
your ultimate hedge against political instability
and economic turmoil
introducing the silver prepper bar
crafted from 0.999
pure silver
and proudly made in the USA
this tangible, divisible asset
can come in handy even in the toughest of times
portable, perforated
and easily tradable
the silver prepper bar is your lifeline
in times of crisis
when facing inflation, currency devaluation
and financial meltdown
silver prepper bars provide peace of mind
don't wait for disaster to strike
secure your future today
with the exclusive silver prepper bar
the only silver bar in the market
divisible into three different size pieces
for maximum utility
all while fitting in your wallet
the smart choice for savvy investors
and preppers alike
with silver prepper bars
you're ready for whatever tomorrow brings
they would run up to the bamboo fence
and they would be shooting between the bamboo
buildings, you know, and just shooting inside
the wanted man is Joseph Coney
charged with abducting huge
numbers of children
forcing them to kill and mutilate
innocent victims
somebody had to pay the price
Sam did that
Sam's children never stop because
the bad things never stop
there is only one Sam's children
there is no one else like him in the world
and I said to him, I said would you
go now to get Coney in the Congo
he says we'll have it down in a second
now it's the DRC, tell us what's happening
to children in the DRC
you have ISIS there, you have Islamic State
and you have ADF
they say Joseph Coney is still alive
he's in the Congo and now God has me
in the Congo
so hopefully we'll meet up one day
but maybe
I can lead him to the Lord
or send him there, one or the other
alright welcome back to the Big Big Show
here we host Lance Migliaccio
George Valentin and our guest
John Kiriakou
man I got that right again, I'm proud of myself
you're not a roller George
I am right, you know what I did, I wrote his name down
but I broke it down into syllables right in front of me
I love it, it's good
you got a flash card
you're doing better than I am
look this is what I did, I'm not lying
let's talk about
social media and all the crap that comes with it
because we have a gentleman that's going to try to
take it by storm here
or brave man, I'm going to say that
thank you for that
social media is a bitch
no I'm not going to say stupid
brave
because
there's still censorship going on, even on X
there is
people are getting
their counts are being throttled
all our counts are being throttled
still Facebook
TikTok is probably the biggest one
right now I'm going to say
Instagram but
tell us, I mean
what made you jump into this field
what inspired you
you know I feel like
maybe I was even pushed into it
no
when the whole weight of the US government
falls on your head
right and
you're in these proffer meetings with the justice department
and they're telling you
take a deal
Mr. Kiriakou and you may live
to meet your grandchildren
exact words
and I know that is 100% accurate
they will threaten you
that you're never going to see the light of day
that if you want to see
your child grow up
you better take this deal
it's the last deal you ever see if you don't
here comes the superseding indictment
we're going to hit you with additional charges
and we're going to hit you with concurrent criminal
appraise or RICO or racketeering
or in your case
foreign agency
violations or you name it but go ahead
and that was the Barack Obama
justice department
which of course was duplicated by
Joe Biden
so
I kind of fell into this
accidentally when I went to prison
the day that I left for prison one of my attorneys said
when you feel comfortable
write me a letter
and I'll send it around to these
600 people who signed up
for a listserv
they're interested in knowing how you're doing
I said okay great
so I waited about six weeks
once I got to prison
I wrote this thing
not even realizing I was exposing
two crimes
that were being committed in the prison
by the guards
I sent it to my lawyer
I didn't know that Ariana
she put it on the Huffington Post
2 million hits
in the next couple of days
next thing I know Jake Tappers
come into the prison to interview me
NPR came to the prison to interview me
Playboy
The Economist, The Atlantic Monthly
I gave more interviews
than you could shake a stick out
and what facility were you at?
this was the Federal Correctional Institution
FCI at Loretto, Pennsylvania
okay
you know one of the things they did
when I was being sentenced
is that a low or is that a camp?
it was a low
interesting they put you low because you should have had
a zero to one offense level
I did, I had a zero
so they put a management variable on you
that's exactly what they did
I was just gonna say it
the judge
my attorneys asked the judge to
send me to a minimum security work camp
and the Justice Department
the Justice Department had no
problem with it
and I go to turn myself in
they put me in the actual prison
because behind the scenes
the Department of Justice
or the agents on your case
sent letters to the BLP
they said this guy
can't be trusted he'll walk off the camp
he has the ability
he speaks three or four different foreign languages
he hit it on the head
he understands multiple identities
he's worked for the CIA
at different levels
he's trained in counter-terrorist techniques
he may not look at these
extremely dangerous
for your guards and staff
I guarantee you if you put in
in a FOIA
did they send it to you?
and they were so stupid they sent it to me
I gotta tell you something
I'm shocked you got it
because those FOIAs they usually wipe their butts with them
excuse my language
what they did either somebody was
particularly stupid
at the BLP
or they took pity on me
because I got a bunch of
so what did it say did I nail it?
it was stamped at the top and the bottom
FOIA exempt do not release
to inmate
and then they released it all to me
and did I nail it?
is it exactly what they were saying about you?
you hit it on the head
and then there was one
page and it was in these huge block
letters and it was it was from
four days before I arrived at the prison
it was from the warden
to all staff and it says
caution inmate has
access to the media
and I thought you know what
there's a future here
there's a future in the media
and so I went for it
yeah you know it's interesting
and let's I want to backpedal here for a minute
I want to talk about you've written eight books
since you've you know I don't know when you started writing
that's really proficient as an
author
I guess you said you're most popular but currently
is the Convenient Terrorist
you want to tell us about that book?
Convenient Terrorist I started off with the Reluctant Spy
that was published in 2010
it got me in all kinds of trouble with the agency
even though I had it cleared
I actually got an espionage charge
from writing that book
after they cleared it
then I wrote one called
and I should say the Reluctant Spy
made number five on the New York Times
bestsellers list that's great
I was very fortunate then
I did doing time like a spy
how the CIA taught me to survive
and thrive in prison and I won
one of the big four literary awards for that
I won the Penn First Amendment award which
no that's a great award
with the Penn Faulkner
the Pulitzer and the Edgar Allen Poe
it's one of the big four and then I did
this one the Reluctant
sorry the Convenient Terrorist
it's about
the Abiz-O-Beta Capture
the Abiz-O-Beta Torture
and then Torture at Guantanamo
Life at Guantanamo
and then I did a series
of four that were commissioned
called the CIA Insiders Guides
I did the Insiders Guide to the Iran Crisis
the CIA Insiders Guide
to Surveillance and Surveillance Detection
to Lying and Lie Detection
and the CIA Insiders Guide
to Disappearing and Living off the Grid
and then I did one for myself
just because I
was interested
I did one called Remains of the Day
the Ultimate Guide
to Washington D.C.'s Historic Cemetery
and
it's coming out in a couple of weeks
but the publisher liked it so much
they commissioned four more
they commissioned the Mafia Graves
of New York City
America's Most Notorious Serial Killers
the Historic Cemetery
of Chicago
and the Country Western Graves
of Nashville
so I got a lot of work to do
I don't sleep very much in all seriousness
Yeah, we don't either
I think whenever you're in media
especially if you're an investigative journalist
it's really not convenient to sleep
you have to do it
people don't realize the amount of time
that goes into what you're doing
so now I have another question
because you brought up Gitmo, right?
Why the hell did we build another courthouse
to make it bigger if we're not putting anybody in it?
You know, that's a great question
and there's a little bit of background
in March
late March of 2002
we had literally
filled the Raul Pindi Pakistan
jail with al-Qaeda prisoners
and so
the head of counterterrorism
at the Pakistani Intelligence Service
the ISI came to me and said
look, the jail's full, you got to do something
with these guys
so I called headquarters and told them
the jail's full, the PACs want us to get these guys out
what should I do with them?
and my colleague on the other end said
put them on a C-12 and send them to Guantanamo
and I said, Guantanamo, Cuba?
Why would we send them to Cuba?
and he said, well we came up
with this idea
we're going to keep them in Guantanamo
for six weeks
we're going to divide them up
and then we're going to send them to the federal district
courts where it makes the most sense
to try them
because 9-11 was still an open criminal investigation
so we're going to send them to the Eastern District of Virginia
the District of D.C
Western District of Pennsylvania
and the Southern and Eastern Districts of New York
and the Eastern District of Massachusetts
I said that's a great idea
and then somebody in Dick Cheney's
office, we don't know who
but we're not sure
said, you know what, these guys are all in Guantanamo
they don't have any rights there
let's just leave them there
like forever
and that's how Guantanamo became
the Guantanamo that we know today
okay, now we've gone from
almost 800 prisoners
in Guantanamo down to 34
these are 34
of which like 20
are genuine bad guys
who should never be released
we're stuck with Guantanamo
because
Congress passed a law
and
Barack Obama
signed it into law
saying that
we can never close Guantanamo
and we can never transfer the prisoners
in Guantanamo to prisons in the United States
in the continental
states
so we're stuck with it
Donald Trump came up with this idea
to send people to Guantanamo
it would
have worked out to be temporarily
and then
it just didn't
the fact of the matter is
these morons at Guantanamo
are not equipped
to handle prisoners
in great numbers over the long term
you can put people there temporarily
but in terms of just
babies sitting there
for years
it's not that kind of a facility
I went to Guantanamo in the summer
let me think
the summer of 2002
when we had hundreds
of people there
and even then
there was a real desire
to process these people
and just get them out
either to third country prisons
or release to their home countries
or whatever just get them processed
and get them out
but Guantanamo
it's not prepared to handle
a facility like that
they're just not good at it
yeah
you know
and people
get confused
they don't realize that the levels of training
for something like that
oh my god
and we see it right
what I was doing years ago
you get some special operators in
taking a hallway
with a knife
and you were trying to show them a disarm
and you realize that
even though they were a special forces team member
they might not be very skilled in that particular arena
they might have been better
with small arms
and as far as shooting
a lot of times they were very skilled
but as far as a lot of the hand to hand take down techniques
and things like that
I was often surprised how
they weren't very skilled in those areas
they might have been hitting the weight pile
and they were good but when it came to the actual
hand to hand strikes
and throat strikes and hitting to the temple
they just didn't know a lot of that stuff
so some people come away
and they think okay well that's an AVCO
that's a special operator
he must be that skilled
but now you've taken those guys
of course the US government's invested
hundreds and hundreds and millions of dollars
and potentially depending on how long the term they've been in
and then you take the average military
and he's made a security guard
or otherwise in any of these facilities
he's not really equipped to handle
you know anything that comes up
I'm sure there's lots of actionable intel
that was lost because people
just handled the detainee
because maybe the detainee wanted to cooperate
and everybody's like shut the fuck up
you know and meanwhile maybe the guy
was trying to hand you the farm
let me ask you this
I don't know if you know who Richard Gage is
he's an architect that runs a group of
that has fully investigated
9-11 he's been on our show
very very good guy really done the homework
in fact he's got some new
information on a
thermite light product
that seemed to be in vast amounts
discovered in the rubble of
the twin towers
what do you think I mean I don't know if you've heard anything
I've heard things there's lots of
questions and of course
knowing a lot about EOD
and knowing a lot about
demolition
you know the take down
the buildings is especially steel buildings
plane jet fuel
that many floors you know the audio
and video what do you think
do you think that it was a combination
story that maybe in fact
some of the things related to 9-11 weren't
as they seem it wasn't all just about
the planes or about
the individuals that supposedly were involved
that maybe there was a much bigger plan
behind the scenes because of course
after 9-11 you know it allowed them
at a minimum to use
Dennis Montgomery to create
a surveillance system
the hammer super computer
and the hammer exploit which were very
effective in surveilling
foreign adversaries but of course
then they were weaponized moved to Fort
Creek, Fort Washington
Obama had a back door to them
and of course they use it to spy
on everything from FISA court
judges to regular American citizens
members of the what do you think
do you think 9-11 there's more to the story
that the American public doesn't know
you know I never did before
I don't believe that it was
the Israelis I don't believe that it was
you know the Saudi Royal family
as to the collapse of the towers
I don't know I'm not an architect
but
I do know from
not just insiders at NSA
but but famed
high level whistleblowers
like Tom Drake and Bill Binney
and Kirk Webe
that NSA was not just
waiting for something like 9-11 to happen
they were salivating at the thought of 9-11
happening because it allowed them
to then begin to intercept
literally every communication
by every American
correct
emails, text messages
phone calls
and then to have it stored
in a facility in the Utah desert
that is so
significant, has so much memory
built in that it can store
enough information
on every American to last for 500 years
so
you know just like the Warren commission
the 9-11 commission
didn't
really reveal anything to us
if anything had hid information from us
like I say like the Warren
commission
it was all insiders
who were members of it
they weren't allowed to interview
CIA case officers
they weren't allowed to interview Guantanamo prisoners
they weren't allowed to address
the issues that you're raising
right now
as to the towers
is that what exposed the government man
it's interesting
one of the problems I have
is that the government in general has become a giant bully
in its own way
in DC
what I don't like about it is
I don't need another mother and father
my mom is still alive
but I already had one
I don't need anybody to tell me
it's national security interest
when it comes to P. Diddy
or the Epstein files
or 9-11
or JFK or MLK
I don't need that
I don't need curated discovery
because it makes me suspicious
I'm sure you are in yourself
you've probably already been impacted in a way
you can call it PTSD
but I don't react the same way as other people
I don't have that issue
I don't not sleep at night
but I know that my behavior is different
I'm sure even George has to deal with it at times
not him so much
but not at all him
but I have a suspicious nature
I'm quick to analyze something
and say this is what I think they're really doing
or what's really going on
otherwise
you can't help it
you've been conditioned
I'm sure you'll have love's dog in your own way
I was diagnosed with severe PTSD
and when it comes to the government
and them telling me
that they have to have a thousand FBI agents
going through the Epstein files
that they've had literally for years
and years and years already
we already know the list
because of the Lolita airplane list
we already know who went
to read DAC stuff
go fuck yourself
I debated Alan Dershowitz
day before yesterday
on the Pierce Morgan show
and I'll tell ya man
this guy
did you ask him about what he's doing with Epstein
he volunteered it
but of course
it was completely whitewashed
it's a dark label
Dershowitz is sophisticated
he's highly articulate
but I have to be honest
he's always given me a slimy vibe
well he kept his underwear on
remember that
yeah he kept his underwear on
exactly
and that makes a difference
yeah that was his claim
he kept his underwear on
although I have to be honest
I don't want to see Alan Dershowitz in his underwear
no thank you
if there is surveillance video
I want to see if the FBI is watching our show
please do not release Alan Dershowitz
in his underwear video if you have it
just keep it
imagine public we don't need to know
I don't want to see Alan Dershowitz in his underwear dude
he probably wears some tidy whiteies
no come on dude
you know it's going to come up in the feed
on all social media
let's switch gears here because I want to make sure
I give you a fair amount of time
let's talk about Panquake
let's talk about why you did it
why you think it's the killer
in the scenes and why you think
they froze your bank accounts
no
yeah Panquake is
a wonderful startup
tech
firm it's a tech software
firm you know originally
it was meant to be a new social media
platform and it's become so much more
than that it's not just
an upstart social media platform that is
going to compete directly with the likes of
twitter and blue sky
mastodon etc etc
but they've also developed
for example link shortners
so the idea is
big tech will follow
you
everywhere you go all around the internet
and so if you don't want to be
followed you can go to it's called link me
and it's
available right there on the Panquake website
you can get a link shortener
put that in your browser
and the big tech companies
can't track you
the reason why I got involved in
Panquake besides the fact that
I know and I like
and I trust the people
involved Susie Dawson is the
chief products officer
she's essentially the founder
of the company
but the reason besides liking and trusting
them is I believe
very very strongly
in security and privacy
and it's none of the government's business
what I look at
on the internet
we all know
that with metadata they can build
a case against anybody they want
even when there is no case to build
they can essentially make it all up
they can fabricate anything they want
I mean you could be doing research
I could type in thermite
I'm doing research because there's a guest that I might have on
that Richard Gage has got
in thermite and sophisticated versions of thermite
and they turn it into
look at him he's looking for thermite
that means he's going to blow up a building
exactly that's all it takes
and so this whole idea
was apparently a threat
to
powerful individuals
maybe governments
and so
they froze our bank accounts
now the bank accounts are in Iceland
and so
it's like a WikiLeaks style thing
and we hired WikiLeaks
Iceland attorneys
and so we ended up winning
that in that the
money was unfrozen
now this freezing
set us back a little bit in terms of our
product rollouts but that's okay
that's okay because
we've won at each step of the way
I think we're going to continue to win
but you know there's got to be
there's got to be a payment
to the piper here
you can't just
freeze companies back accounts
if you don't like the fact that they're trying to
do something to address your
surveillance
you know people don't want to be surveilled
people want privacy
and just as an aside
and my colleagues at Pankwaker probably
stick with hearing me say this
but here's how cool this company is
not only is it focused on privacy
not only is it focused on
transparency the code is open code
for example
but it's even a green country
where they use
thermal energy
from underground
hot springs
in Iceland
to power the servers
so it's completely green on top of all of it
but the bottom line is
this is really about personal privacy
it's about security
it's about governmental
and corporate transparency
it's all wrapped into one product
and that is a threat to important
and powerful entities
yeah you know
Eric Prince is a friend of ours he's been on the show
from Blackwater
I want to compliment him on his unplugged
phone by the way I'm going to buy one this week
I was about to comment on that it's interesting
the unplugged phone
which of course not only has an operating system
that isn't
that's been created not to track you
but also the hardware
the way he's assembled the phone
and making sure
that there are no back doors
in any of the hardware he's using
they actually construct the phone
very sophisticated appliance
and my opinion is
pretty amazing in the fact that
of course he's even had some fallout
behind the scenes of people reacting
that he's creating a phone that
you know doesn't allow you to be
geofenced 24-7
dropped on
you know people are ignorant
of course they just want to be able to go on social media
and take selfies of their dessert
not realizing that maybe
all those things are tracking you on one another
they also think it's
well it's interesting that people have told me
oh just talk to me on signal
number one I'm never going to talk on any appliance
I'd have to be butt ass naked
in a steam room
with a towel over the glass door
so they couldn't pick up the vibrations
if I wanted to have that kind of a dialogue
Lance hold on I want to ask some questions
because I'm shocked that you did not ask him
this question when it came to social media
yeah and you know what question I'm going to ask
so on your site people are posting
they're promoting I don't know they're putting
political ads that are being paid for
do they have to put on there that this is
a paid
they're being paid to post this
because that's like a pet peeve with Lance
like on X because
let me give you a little more background
maybe just a hair more background
he knows he says a good question
I'm over I'm blown away
by the first of all I don't like these operations
I don't like these brainwashing operations
that start and I don't care whether you
call it deep state cabal
uniparty I don't give a shit that start at the
top of the food chain and they get funneled
mainstream media they go to the
politicals and the daily beast and the
Washington Post and then the next wave
is the social media influences are getting paid
and they're being sponsored by act blue
that agency out of Chicago and other
groups to post a certain narrative
and then of course here come the body counts next
you know activating and commenting
and sharing and liking so they can propel it up
what I don't like about it is that all these
social media influences like we heard just recently
that Bill Crystal I could never figure
out John and then I'll let you comment
for me I can't have
negativity around me constantly right I already
have dark thoughts as it is I don't want
to be a negative in my daily life I don't want
to be negative George and I don't post a
negative angry content we don't get angry
about stuff because I just don't need that
I'm already dark enough without the help of that
so I look at a social media influence of
everything they post is Trump's a piece
of shit Elon Musk sucks
you know this senator's a piece this
Republican senator's a piece of crap
Magus sucks and they do that all day
long I always ask myself well how can you
do that right how can you sit there
posting that negatively all day long
doesn't it doesn't just drain your soul
this is what I'm thinking now I know
he's not posting
he probably takes the 8 million
pay some kid 100 grand a year
and he's like hey I'm going to make 7.9
this year doing absolutely
nothing so it's probably not even
him posting that's so now it's all crystal
clear to me I think that the social
media platforms have a requirement
and when you look at FCC law and
FTC law it's very clear if
you're being paid or giving anything
of value to post anything
you're supposed to say paid post
sponsored by sponsored post
even if it's a video short form content
you're supposed to open
with saying this video paid for by act blue
you're exactly not doing it
no they're not doing it
so is it a loophole
or are they violating the law
they're violating the law
yeah I think you're right
I mean if it was you and I
if they wanted to come after you
they wanted to come after you
so on your platform
how would you would you
combine that or just leave it be
or how would you combat that
that's a good question
I'm not exactly sure
I think there's an obligation
to make it clickable like we have a sponsor
we have Genesis Gold Group we have original
Glory beer you know rumble does stuff for us
we make it very clear because I want
the audience to realize it's transparent
I'm not being paid by Panquake to promote
Panquake I would tell people listen
we have them on the show because we think John's got great information
you do you're an amazing guest
and I think the opportunity for you to talk
about your platform why successful but I think
I think it's a big deal
I think you're right
I think you're exactly right
you know one of the other things too about Panquake
is that there's no algorithm
that that directs traffic
this is something that they were very serious about
from the very beginning from when they were first
writing the code
there is no algorithm so if you write
if you write a you know
a submission a tweet whatever
a Quake whatever
it goes to your for you it might be a tremor
yeah tremor right
right a little
a little bit of a shift
yeah it'll go to the people who follow you
it's not going to be
it's not going to be tagged by some bot
and then distributed to a billion people
or it's not going to be suppressed
which is the other side of this
you know
but the crack head nature
of social media right
that people base their
not us we're promoting our show
that's really what it is about for us
promoting our show promoting our radio show
but people want that engagement
they want to know they're going to get
replies and comments so they want to know
that if the post is appreciated
by their followers that it'll end up
in the search string
that it'll get more activity because again
if it's popular with your followers it should be
popular with the other people on PanQuake
and that's kind of what social media is
of course we see the suppression on X
you know I assume that you guys
don't have any suppression algorithms
built into the back end correct absolutely nothing
yeah that's a big deal
because it's still out there
it's all over Instagram it's all over Facebook
it's all over X still
I mean I wish Elon Musk would doge
his own company yeah seriously right
yeah you know that's another thing
if I could bring this up
it's Schellenberger and
it was like three of them
Matt Taibbi
when they went over to Twitter
at Elon Musk's invitation
and revealed the Twitter files
one of the things that they revealed was
this presence
at Twitter
and we later learned at Facebook
at Instagram at all of the
social media platforms of either
current or former FBI
CIA and NSA officers
my own boss
when I came back from Athens in
2000 I worked for a guy
I won't say his name but he left
after about six months and I said where are you going
he said Microsoft I said Microsoft
what are you gonna do Microsoft
he said some really cool social media stuff
and I was like
I don't even know what social media is
or I didn't in 2000
but from the
beginning they were thinking of getting
all these CIA and FBI people
and a handful of NSA people
and putting them in the companies
themselves well
now we know thanks to these great journalists
that
a lot of it was just to carry out
suppression or to carry out
warrantless spying
right another thing that they do
is let's say the FBI wants to
build a case against you
against the two of you
rather than to go to
a judge and get a warrant
which is what you're supposed to do
they just go directly to
the social media company
and they buy your data
it's for sale
you don't need a warrant to buy it
and so they just cut a check
and they get all your data
and you're none the wiser
which if you think about it
is a clear constitutional violation
because any kind of surveillance
they're supposed to obviously
submit for a warrant
it doesn't matter what it is
but let's face it
they think that warrants at this point
and the constitution are an inconvenience
they don't follow it
because there's no consequences
and no accountability
you just can't expect that
listen John I know we're out of time for today
because we've got two other shows to do today
but I would just want to say number one
first of all thank you very much
I'd like to have you on our nationally syndicated radio show
so we're definitely going to have a discussion about that
to figure out a schedule
George was right away and goes
let's get him on the radio show
at the very beginning
after you talked for the first couple of weeks
let's get him on the radio show
so let's do that
Panquake
let me do this, give them the shameless plug
where do they buy your books
where do they follow you on social media
I appreciate involved with Panquake
anything you want to throw at them
this is the shameless plug slot
it's easy, it's Panquake
like P-A-N-Q-U-A-K-E dot com
it's all self-explanatory
I do a TV show
on a platform called Unified TV
it's U-N-I-F-Y-D
C-I-A Declassified
we take declassified documents
and tell historic stories about the C-I-A's
involvement in these international events
I'm on Twitter
I'm on Facebook
and Substack
everything I do I put on Substack
I'll put a link to this on Substack
it's JohnKyriaku.substack.com
and the books are all on Amazon
so thanks very much for that
yeah we appreciate that man
thank you so very much for joining us
Trevor Fitzgibbons, thank you
great guest, we appreciate all the help
Trevor's amazing, we love him
we've been doing stuff with him for years
so of course if you like the show
thumbs up, comment share
George will be making short form content
use it anyway you want
on any of your websites, social media
George can interact with you
it will also be available in 25 languages
closed caption on Rumble
if you like the show and you can do a paid subscription
great, if you can do a Rumble rant
great, if you can do a thumbs up
if there's other guests you'd like to see us get on the show
let us know in the chat
now don't forget today
1pm Global Finance Forum
the number one finance show on Rumble
we'll be doing that right after this
shortly thereafter
Crypto Power Hour
the number one crypto show on Rumble
we have a great guest today
Michael Markowski, you're going to want to hear what he has to say
really interesting guy when it comes to algorithms
and what's going to be happening in the crypto world
and what's going on in the finance world
with what he does
George, what are the stuff you want to share with the audience before we head out
let's see
John I just found John next and followed you
I don't know if you're on TikTok
if you are, because I do the short form
and I'll tag you on all that stuff in TikTok
everywhere
I just want to wish everybody a happy Easter
you know spend the time with your families
praise Jesus Christ
because he is king
we'll see you at 1 o'clock and 3 o'clock
if not stay blessed, stay healthy
and stay frosty
catch y'all later
if we lose freedom here
there is no place
to escape to
this is the last stand on earth
as an American
who keeps up with the real news
you know by now the severity
of the economic issues that are plaguing
our great nation
my name is Jonathan Rose and I'm the CEO
of Genesis Gold Group
the only major faith driven company
in the industry
2024 is a year full of uncertainties
with trillions of dollars
in national debt
inflation impacting your savings
and the pivotal election year
the face of mind is more valuable than ever
now is the time to use
physical gold and silver to preserve
your hard-earned retirement savings
with a gold IRA
call Genesis Gold Group today
our team has decades of experience
helping folks just like you take their first step
on the path to true financial freedom
with a gold and silver IRA
call Genesis Gold Group today
at 1-800-200-GOLD
for a no commitment informative consultation
with one of our experts to find out if we can be a fit for you
call now at 1-800-200-4653
or visit
GenesisGoldGroup.com
in a world of uncertainty
be prepared with silver prepper bars
your ultimate hedge against
political instability and economic turmoil
introducing the silver prepper bar
crafted from 0.999
pure silver and proudly
made in the USA this tangible
divisible asset can come in handy
even in the toughest of times
portable, perforated
and easily tradable the silver prepper bar
is your lifeline in times of crisis
when facing inflation
currency devaluation
and financial meltdown
silver prepper bars provide peace of mind
don't wait for disaster to strike
secure your future today
with the exclusive silver prepper bar
the only silver bar in the market
divisible into three different size pieces
for maximum utility
all while fitting in your wallet
the smart choice for savvy investors
like with silver prepper bars
you're ready for whatever tomorrow brings
they would run up to the bamboo fence
and they would be shooting
between the bamboo at the buildings
you know and just shooting inside
the wanted man is Joseph Coney
charged with abducting huge
numbers of children
forcing them to kill and mutilate
innocent victims
somebody had to pay the price
Sam did that
Sam children's never stopped because
there is only one Sam
children there is no one else like him
in the world and I said to him
I says would you go now
to get Coney in the Congo
he says without a doubt in a second
now it's the DRC tell us what's happening
to children in the DRC
you have ISIS there you have Islamic State
and you have ADF
hey St. Joseph Coney is still alive
he's in the Congo and now God has me in the Congo
you know so hopefully
we'll meet up one day
but maybe I can
lead him to the Lord
or send him there one or the other